first things first i want to tell you
that you should only withdraw your vul
number one if you've reached the goals
you originally said tanda and you bought
a vul
for a certain goal maybe you would want
to
raise or save up money and invest for
the education of your kids for your
retirement for a big goal in the future
not achieve monobayon that's the first
reason why
and
probably the
the most important reason why you should
withdraw your vol
the second reason if it's beyond 10
years
if it's beyond 10 years
i'm sure all the ul's don't have
withdrawal charges anymore so if it's
beyond 10 years and then the rich money
in goldman
s third reason
uh would probably be that you understand
that there are withdrawal charges if you
are withdrawing
less than 10 years balance especially if
less than five years banana definitely
there will be withdrawal charges meaning
aside from the policy charges
70 000
but withdrawing 70 000 we charge payon
no so
if you don't understand that fully
then maybe you're
you you know you're making a decision na
kulang yung information
so you should
with you should be able to withdraw your
with your bul if you understand that
there are
withdrawal charges possibly and already
accepted
your mind is at peace with that
then okay you can withdraw your vol
and the fourth thing
probably the most important is that
you have other
insurance
policies you have other life insurance
policies that are in force
why because there's a lot of vul
that we got but we understand the
merondinian life insurance
coverage some
may know critical illness coverage so in
shrinka as the policy owner
but we need view elbow in full signal
all those benefits
will be you know
will be removed
right it will all be cancelled
so you are now the uninsured
life insurance benefit in case of death
for your family to continue their
lifestyle
critical illness coverage or
hospitalization benefit just in case you
get sick somehow
so if you don't have other insurance
policies
maybe it's the wrong
information you're getting the wrong
information you're withdrawing for the
wrong reason
but so if you have other insurance
policies and then
you el nato
because it's really for accumulation
then maybe go ahead right do it
[Music]
you